The future awaits.
Bill & Ted Face the Music is a comedy, science fiction,
adventure film directed by Dean Parisot.
Yet to fulfill their rock and roll destiny, the stakes are higher than ever for the now middle-aged Bill and Ted who set out
on a new adventure when a visitor from the future warns them that only their song can save life as we know it.
Ted, played by Keanu Reeves.
Bill, played by Alex Winter.
Kelly, played by Kristen Schaal.
Thea, played by Samara Weaving.
Billie, played by Jack Haven.
Death, played by William Sadler.
Bill & Ted Face the Music is a 2020 American science fiction comedy film
directed by Dean Parisot and written by Chris Matheson and Ed Solomon.
It is the third film in the Bill & Ted film series, and the
sequel to Bill & Ted's Bogus Journey (1991).
Alex Winter, Keanu Reeves, and William Sadler reprise their roles as Bill, Ted, and the Grim Reaper, respectively; while Kristen Schaal, Samara
Weaving, Jack Haven, Anthony Carrigan, Erinn Hayes, Jayma Mays, Holland Taylor, Kid Cudi, Jillian Bell and Beck Bennett join the cast.
In the film, Bill and Ted must write a song to unite
humanity before space-time is destroyed.
The script was laid out as early as 2010, but a
production deal was not confirmed until 2018.
Filming commenced on July 1, 2019.
Bill & Ted Face the Music was simultaneously released in theaters and through Premium
VOD in the United States on August 28, 2020, by United Artists Releasing.
It received generally positive reviews from critics for the performances and
story, with many calling it a welcome return to form for the series.
The film explores themes of guitar, time travel, sequel,
aftercreditsstinger, father daughter relationship.
The tone is lighthearted and thought_provoking.